Wthough
Am I just joking now?
In this program, the representative
members
will talk about various things
​​
twond part
third
last
The day which can't say the truth
Hi everyone…
We have takoyaki today, you know?
I thought it's cold out but it was
pretty warm though...
Thank you for watching.
Takoyaki!
Which one should I eat?
I heard that there is a sauce and salt.
Listen to this.
It's 1 pm now.
How luxurious it is!
I wonder if I can eat it all.
I want to eat it.
I changed my clothes.
Bye-bye.
They continue the shooting to make
Suretyi busy.
The stage is so cute!
It's very cute.
Everyone's there!
It's huge!
Thank you.
Wow!
Is this the place?
Yes.
Thank you.
The person who breaks the wall with her
power
will be the loser.
So, please be careful.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
To the hearts of the staff, rock on!
We are Super-excited-CNN!
Thank you.
Let's do it.
I wish you all the best.
Shall we go get impact, You can't save
us
It was a tremendous dragon ball with
dangerous events.
Show me what you got.
I don't know anything
Chan, chan, chan, chan, chan, let's go!
I'm 70 years old, I can't be a student
I should think about it
I'm a little doubtful
Chan, chan, chan, chan, chan, let's go!
I want to be a Kyoto student
And be careful of the back, darling
Yes
I don't know anything
I'm 70 years old, I'm not a student
I'm not thinking about it
I'm 80 years old, I'm still a student
I want to be a student
Wait a minute, I'm not a student
I realized it
I'm a student
Please tell me who I am
I want to be a student
Wait a minute, I'm not a student
I realized it
I'm a student
Please show me,
Wishing, just wish
Thank you for watching!
2020讀very perfume
allergy
How 하면
before
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Do your best!
Let's talk.
Okay.
You're already surprised?
Thank you for coming.
Please support us.
We will come back next week.
Bye-bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.
This time, I'm using a vertical screen.
I'm always in the frame.
I can't make a weird face.
I'm going to put on a new color.
I'm about to cry.
You can sit here.
Thank you.
I was thinking about something.
It's a big deal.
To be continued.
Wow!
I'm so excited to see the first song of
the commercial.
I'm excited to see the person behind
the camera.
I'm so excited.
Wow!
I'm going to fix my makeup.
Let's sing and let loose
That's what you said
The Brooklyn mapping practice was a
success!
I'm Kageyama.
I'm so nervous.
I'll do my best.
Please.
I'm so excited.
I ate a lot of delicious food.
I'll do my best.
The first day of the shoot
I'm pretty picky with my words.
I'm sure you're lying.
The second day of the shoot
Let's go!
The third day of the shoot
I can't think of anything else.
I'm not a director.
Don't remember.
I'll be told.
I'm not a director.
If you get caught, you'll be exposed.
The way I look changes.
I'm not like Hachie.
Wait a minute.
Please relax.
Relax?
Not yet.
I'm not a director.
English summar.
I'm not sure if I can say it.
You can't.
I'm angry, but I can't help it.
Why?
Because I'm looking back.
I don't know if you can't see it.
Maybe she thinks so.
I can't speak naturally.
I'm crazy about you.
Please wait a moment.
Do you know?
Yes, I do.
It smells good.
It smells so good.
Ok, then, let's start.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
Today, we're going to record the hall
of the Super Tokimeki Sennae Club.
I'm sorry.
Let me do it again.
Thank you for coming to the Spring 33
Hall Rock concert 2022 of the Super
Tokimeki Promotion Club and the Super
Tokimeki Promotion Club.
I'm Kanami, the super Tokimeki blue,
and I'm Angelia, the super Tokimeki
purple.
Before we start the performance, I'd
like to ask the audience to be careful
of the line.
The audience in the first and second
rows will stand up within their seats
and enjoy the performance.
Thank you for your time.
No loud cheering or jumping.
Please enjoy the show with your hands
and feet.
We will be back soon.
We are so excited.
We will make you enjoy the show.
Let's enjoy together.
Thank you.
Please wait for us.
Tanomi! Junia! Koko! Haruka! Aki!
Hiyori!
Super-Fan-Fan-Sign-Dance!
Rock'n'Roll!
I'm going home.
NAKAMAZE
This is wafer rice roll!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!
I'm happy just to be in moments like
that
The more I cry, the more I laugh
Today is brighter than anyone else
It's the sun of emotions in my dreams
I've already realized the true meaning
of excitement
I understand everything
You and my heartbeat
I'll look up at the sky
Yay! Yay!
It's over!
Osaka Takoyaki!
Yes, it's over!
Thank you for the meal!
We finished the first day of the
concert!
It was great.
Thank you so much.
It's been a while since we had such a
warm welcome.
We were clapping so hard.
We were clapping while drinking water.
Thank you so much.
We should drink it up.
It was great.
We sang a lot of youthful songs.
We sang a lot of love songs.
Please support us.
We can do our best tomorrow.
Let's do our best.
Please look forward to it.
Please come and see us.
See you.
Bye bye.
Metabolic ring.
I'm going to dance.
Thank you for watching!
I don't need to step on the brakes or
anything and rolling at full speed,
So stay with me, Toki Senrise!
Takashi no mainichi war kommun lou da
da da da...
SKIP SKIP SKIPbaby Tokyo
Kimi ga Kimi de Doctor
Arutamenno sontai
I love you, doctor
I can't stop, cry cry cry
I'm loving you more than I can control
Let's get high!
Enjoy the taste of the things I've made
I want to love you more and more
More and more than I can imagine
One, two, three!
I can't stop, cry cry cry
lol
If you like this video, if you think
it's cute, if you want to get a special
point, please subscribe to our channel
and give us a high rating.
Thank you.
Please leave a comment.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I wonder why, when I smile, it's as if
the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and be at
ease
If I don't, I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I'm sure someone is getting wet
somewhere
I wonder if it's cold
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings a little
bit
A view that I don't know yet in front
of me
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
Draw a piece of the future on the
canvas of my damaged heart
I'll guide you
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember it right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la